Guide to the Stanford University, School of Humanities and Sciences, Innovative Academic Courses, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1992-086
  - End-Quarter Evaluations Winter 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Index of Winter, End-Quarter Evaluations 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Mid-Quarter Evaluations Spring 1979 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Index of Spring Quater Evaluations 1979 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Intr/stud, End Quarter Evaluation Statistics: Fall 1978- Spring 1979 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations Fall 1979 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Index of Fall Quarter Evaluations 1979 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - End-Quarter Evaluations Fall 1979-1979 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations: Winter 1980 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - End Quarter Evaluations Winter 1980 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Index of Winter Quarter Evaluations, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - End Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1980 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Index of Spring Quarter Evaluations, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Spring Quarter Mid Quarter Evaluations, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Fall 1980 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - SWOPSI Final Evaluations for Students (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Index of Fall Quarter Evaluations, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Summary of Instructor Mid Quarter Evaluation, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Winter 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Index of End Quarter Evaluations, Winter 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Summary of Instructor Mid Quarter Evaluations, 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Index of End Quarter Evaluations, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Index of End Quarter Evaluations, Spring Quarter 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Index of End Quarter Evaluations, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Index of End Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Summary of End Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1980- Spring 1982 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Fall Quarter 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Index of End Quarter Evaluations, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Mid-Quarter Evaluations Winter Quarter 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Index of End-Quarter Evaluations, Winter Quarter 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Spring Quarter 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Fall Quarter 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Key to End Quarter Evauations, Fall Quarter 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Winter Quarter 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - End Quarter Evaluations Winter 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations Spring 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Key to End Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Summer Quarter Evaluations, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Mid Quarter Evaulations Fall 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Key To Evaluations, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Key to End Quarter Evaluations, Winter Quarter 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Final Evaluations, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Mid-Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Key to End Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Summary of End Quarter Evaluations, Fall 1985 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Winter 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Final Evaluations, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Summary of End Quarter Evaluations, Fall 1983-Spring 1985 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - End Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Summary of Mid Quarter Evaluations (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Fall 1986-1987 SWOPSI/ UGS/FSS (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - End Quarter Evaluations, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Mid Quarter Evaluations, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - End Quarter Evaluation Winter 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - End Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - SWOPSI Proposed Couses Fall and Winter 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - SWOPSI Proposals Winter and Spring 1972 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - SWOPSI 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Community Land Trust Proposal SWOP 181 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Blue Folder (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Course Proposals Spring 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Course Proposals Fall 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Course Proposals Winter 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Course Proposals Spring 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Course Proposals Fall 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Course ProposalsWinter 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Course Proposals Spring 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Course Proposals Fall 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Course Proposals Winter 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Course Proposals Spring 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Course Proposals Fall 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Course Proposals Winter 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Course Proposals Spring 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Course Proposals Fall 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Course Proposals Winter 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Course Proposals Spring 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Fall Proposals 1980 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Course Proposals Winter 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Course Proposals Winter 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Spring 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Course Proposals Fall 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Course Proposals Winter 19811982 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Course Proposals Spring 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Summer 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Course Proposals Fall 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Course Proposals Winter 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Course Proposals Spring Quarter 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Proposals: 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Proposals Not Approved 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Proposals- Withdrew 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Course Proposals Fall 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Course Proposals Winter 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Course Proposals Spring 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Proposals: 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Course Proposals Fall 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Course Proposals Winter 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Course Proposals Spring 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Proposals: Fall 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Proposals: Spring 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Fall Quarter IAC Proposals 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Course Proposals Winter Quarter 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Winter Quarter Course Proposals, SWOPSI 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Winter Course Proposals 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - FSS Proposals- Winter 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Rejected Proposals Fall 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Approved IAC Course Proposals Winter Quarter 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Course Proposals Winter 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Rejected Course Proposals Winter Quarter 1987 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Approved Proposals Spring 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Course Proposals Spring, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Rejected Proposals for Spring 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Course Proposals Fall 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Rejected Proposals for Winter 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Rejected Proposals Spring Quarter 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Winter Proposals 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Spring Proposals 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - SES Minutes 1972-1973 (1968) (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Policy Board Minutes 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - SWOPSI 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Policy Board Minutes 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Policy Board Minutes 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - NISS Minutes 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Policy Board Minutes 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - SWOPSI Minutes 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Policy Board Minutes 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - PB Minutes 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - PB Minutes 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Policy Board Minutes and Letters 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - C-US Minutes 1977 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - PB Minutes 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Policy Board Minutes and Letters 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - PB Minutes 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board Agenda and Minutes 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Policy Board Minutes and Letters 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - PB Minutes 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Policy Board Minutes and Letters 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - To Within Stanford From SWOPSI (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - AU Correspondence Out 1970 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - ODUS to SWOPSI 1970 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence with Ford 1970 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence from CUS (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - ODUS to SWOPSI 1971 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - AU Correspondence Out 1971 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - ODUS From SWOPSI 1971 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Coordination with Alumni (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Request for Information Outside Stanford 1971 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Foundations- Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Stanford from within Stanford 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - ODUS To SWOPSI 1972 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - ODUS From SWOPSI 1972 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - AU Correspondence Out 1972 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - To Outside Stanford from SWOPSI 1972 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - CIR Liason 1972 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - To SWOPSI from Within Stanford 1972 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - CUS From SWOPSI 1972 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Policy Board Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with Course Leaders 1972 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with the University Fellows 1972 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - To SWOPSI from Outside Stanford 1972 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - ODUS from SWOPSI 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - CUS From SWOPSI 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - SWOPSI from Within Stanford 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - SWOPSI From Odus 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence Outside Stanford From SWOPSI 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - SWOPSI from Outside Stanford 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - ODUS from SWOPSI 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - SWOPSI from Odus 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - SWOPSI from within Stanford 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Within Stanford from SWOPSI 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - SWOPSI From CUS 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Office Memos 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Within Stanford from SWOPSI 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - SWOPSI From CUS 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Outside Stanford from SWOPSI Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Communication Policy Board 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - ODUS From Stanford 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Within Stanford From SWOPSI 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - SWOPSI From Within Stanford 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Outside Stanford From SWOPSI 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - SWOPSI From ODUS 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - ODUS From SWOPSI 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - SWOP From ODUS 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - ODUS From SWOPSI 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Outside Stanford from SWOPSI 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Within Stanford From SWOP 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - SWOP From Within Stanford 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Within Stanford From SWOP 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - SWOP From Within Stanford 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - SWOP From ODUS 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - ODUS From SWOPSI 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Corresponedence 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Outside Stanford From SWOP 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - PB Correspondence 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Within Stanford From SWOPSI 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - SWOPSI From Within Stanford 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - SWOPSI From ODUS 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - ODUS From SWOPSI 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - SWOPSI From Outside Stanford 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - SWOPSI from Within Stanford 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - SWOPSI From ODUS 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - ODUS from SWOPSI 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - Within Stanford from SWOPSI 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  - SWOPSI From Outside Stanford 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  - ODUS from SWOPSI 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 65)
  - SWOPSI from ODUS 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  - Within Stanford from SWOPSI 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 67)
  - SWOPSI from within Stanford, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - SWOPSI from outside Stanford 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 69)
  - SWOPSI from Within Stanford, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 70)
  - Within Stanford From SWOPSI 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 71)
  - ODUS from SWOPSI 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 72)
  - SWOPSI from ODUS 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 74)
  - SWOPSI from Outside Stanford, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence 1981-1983 (Box 37, Folder 76)
  - SWOPSI from Within Stanford, 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 78)
  - SWOPSI from Outside Stanford, 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 79)
  - SWOPSI from H&S 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 80)
  - Within Stanford from SWOPSI 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 81)
  - H&S from Stanford, 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 82)
  - Humanities and Sciences from SWOPSI 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - SWOPSI from Outside Stanford, 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - SWOPSI from Humanities and Sciences 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - SWOPSI from Within Stanford, 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Within Stanford from SWOPSI 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Summer Quarter Business 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - SWOPSI from Within Stanford, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - SWOPSI from Humanities and Sciences 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Humanities and Sciences from SWOPSI 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Within Stanford from IAC 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - IAC From Within Stanford, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - IAC From Humanities and Science, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Humanities and Sciences from IAC 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Correspondnece 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Goal Statement, Summary of Evaluations Fall 1969 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Fall Quarter General 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Winter Quarter General 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - SWOPSI 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Old SWOPSI Materials 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - SWOPSI 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Publishers and Typesetters 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Funding (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - SWOPSI Political Position (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Instructors Fall 1970 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - SWOPSI Workshop Leaders Guide 1970 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Ford Foundation Proposals (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Columbae Publication on War Crimes 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - SWOPSI Proposal for Development During 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Selection of SWOPSI Director Spring 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - SWOPSI Directorship: Nick Corff 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Budget (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - SWOPSI Publicity 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - SWOPSI Budget 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - SWOPSI Reports 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Long Range Plans (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - SWOPSI Reports: Quarterly Reports and Director Reports 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - SWOPSI General 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Application for SWOPSI Director (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - SWOPSI Historical 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - SWOPSI Statistics 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - SWOPSI Evaluations 1969-1972 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Quarterly Report Fall Quarter 1971 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Short Term Appt. Information 1971 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Funding for SWOPSI (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Change to SWOPSI, Senate Meeting, Novemeber 1971 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Provost Willaim F. Miller Notes Re: Leg. Issues Raised by Stanford 1971 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - ODUS General Documents 1971 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Research Interests (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Research Policy 1971 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - SWOP 129 Half Moon Bay and How It will Be Developed (Spring 1971-1972) (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - SWOP 111 Unrest in the Academy: The Case of H Bruce Franklin 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - SWOPSI Symposium on Imperialism 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - SWOPSI Budget 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Academic Planning Office (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - SWOPSI Credit Review Agreements 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Credit Criteria for EDP Courses 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Book Dealers and Distributors 1970-1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - SWOPSI Information Package 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - SWOPSI Charge 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Typists for Hire Also Composter 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Misc. 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - SWOPSI General 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Quarterly Report Winter Quarter 1972 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Spring Quarter Report 1972 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Quarterly Report- Fall, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 125 Intercommunalism 1972 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - SWOPSI Publications Funding 1972 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - SWOPSI Workshop Leaders Guide 1972 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - SWOPSI Publications Program 1972 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Short Term Academic Appointments Fall 1972 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - DOD Volume II 1972 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Provost Miller Document 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - SWOPSI- Senate Charge 1972 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Copies of 1972 Charge Not Approved (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 143 Varsity Athletics and the Black Community and Stanford University Autumn 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Policy Board Procedure/Respond 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Communications Policy Board 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - SWOPSI Credit Review Agreements 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - SWOPSI Budget 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Report on Special Joint Agence 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Charge from Academic Sentate January, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Shockley 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Rational 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - SWOPSI Publications Request 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - SWOPSI General 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - SCIRE Director Search, 1970-1971 Spring/Summer (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Copyright Information to 1973 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Senate Charge 1973 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - SWOPSI Evaluation- Klevansky 1973 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Teaching Tips, etc. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - More Teaching Tips (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Teaching Tips- Discussions (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Shockley 1970-1973 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - University Proposals (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - SWOPSI Stanford Advocacy Project 1973 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - SWOPSI Publication Finances 1970-1974 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Gibbs Stanford Undergraduate Education in the 1970's: A Call for Educating the Whole Person (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - SWOPSI The 60's Program 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Communication; Policy Board 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Externships Proposal 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Files from SWOPSI 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Studies, Stats, EDP 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Copyrights 1972-1974 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - ARLO, Fall, Winter, Spring 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - SWOPSI General 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - SWOPSI Brochures and Course Listings 1970-1974 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - IAC Office Quarterly Routine IAC Instructor Rosters 1989-1992 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - SWOPSI/NISS Teleconferance 8/14/74 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Proposals Fall 1974 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - SWOPSI Director Search 1974 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Sponsorship- Fall, Spring 1974 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Report of the Committee on the Professoriate at Stanford (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - New Director- Spring 1974 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - SWOPSI Hodgson Report 1974 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - SWOPSI - NISS Evaluation 1974 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Policy Board 1974-1975 including debate over UNGRASPEL (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Publications Policy 1974 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board Meetings 1974-195 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - SWOPSI Planning Statement 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - SAVE SWOPSI 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Future of SWOPSI 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - SWOPSI Fight for Life (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Floden Report 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Floden Report 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Sponsorship Leadership Report: Hodgson Report 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Copyright Negotiations (sales, etc.) 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Odus Staff Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - SWOPSI Handbook 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Index of Class Lists 1970-1975 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Black Athletes (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - NISS Conference 1975 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - NISS Conference May 1975 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - NISS SWOPSI Workshop Development Project 1975 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Workshops in Departments 1975 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Ad Hoc Panel on Future of EDP's (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Publications to 1975 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - SWOPSI Events Spring Quarter 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Consumer Issues: Legal and Political 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Film and Lecture Series: Films of Repression and Reaction 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Political Economy of the Environment Film Series 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Communication/ Policy Board 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - SWOPSI Directorship 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - SWOPSI Student Co-Director 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Workshop for Workshop Leaders 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - SWOPSI Handbook 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - NISS Project- Budget 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - NISS 1975-1976 NISS 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - NISS Project Report 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - NISS 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - The Charge 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Hodgson Report 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Plan to Rearrange ODUS 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Bicentennial Perspectives: SWOPSI and ARC 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - SWOPSI Merlyn Paine (Office Assistant) 1971-1976 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Special Events 1976 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Workshop for Working Leaders, October 1976 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Student Co-Director Search Spring 1976 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Draft- SWOPSI Handbook (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Assistant EDP Dean (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Barry Commoner (Box 41, Folder 36)